export default [
{
            id: 1,
            question: 'What is 0 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['1','2','3','0'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 2,
            question: 'What is 0 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['1','1','0','2'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 3,
            question: 'What is 0 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['1','2','1','0'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 4,
            question: 'What is 0 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['1','2','3','0'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 5,
            question: 'What is 0 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['3','1','2','4'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 6,
            question: 'What is 0 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['2','5','4','3'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 7,
            question: 'What is 0 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['6','4','3','5'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 8,
            question: 'What is 0 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['5','6','4','7'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 9,
            question: 'What is 0 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['7','6','5','8'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 10,
            question: 'What is 0 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['7','6','9','8'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 11,
            question: 'What is 1 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['0','1','3','2'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 12,
            question: 'What is 1 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['2','0','1','3'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 13,
            question: 'What is 1 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 14,
            question: 'What is 1 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['1','3','4','2'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 15,
            question: 'What is 1 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['5','3','4','2'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 16,
            question: 'What is 1 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['5','4','3','6'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 17,
            question: 'What is 1 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['4','5','6','7'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 18,
            question: 'What is 1 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['5','8','7','6'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 19,
            question: 'What is 1 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['9','6','8','7'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 20,
            question: 'What is 1 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['7','10','9','8'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 21,
            question: 'What is 2 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['0','2','3','1'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 22,
            question: 'What is 2 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['1','2','0','3'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 23,
            question: 'What is 2 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['2','4','1','3'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 24,
            question: 'What is 2 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['3','4','5','2'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 25,
            question: 'What is 2 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['3','6','4','5'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 26,
            question: 'What is 2 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['5','4','7','6'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 27,
            question: 'What is 2 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['6','8','5','7'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 28,
            question: 'What is 2 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['6','7','8','9'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 29,
            question: 'What is 2 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['9','7','10','8'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 30,
            question: 'What is 2 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['9','10','8','11'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 31,
            question: 'What is 3 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 32,
            question: 'What is 3 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['4','1','2','3'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 33,
            question: 'What is 3 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['4','5','2','3'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 34,
            question: 'What is 3 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['4','3','6','5'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 35,
            question: 'What is 3 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['7','5','6','4'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 36,
            question: 'What is 3 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['5','8','6','7'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 37,
            question: 'What is 3 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['9','8','6','7'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 38,
            question: 'What is 3 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['10','7','9','8'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 39,
            question: 'What is 3 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['11','8','10','9'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 40,
            question: 'What is 3 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['12','11','10','9'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 41,
            question: 'What is 4 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['2','1','3','4'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 42,
            question: 'What is 4 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['5','3','2','4'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 43,
            question: 'What is 4 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['4','6','5','3'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 44,
            question: 'What is 4 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['5','4','7','6'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 45,
            question: 'What is 4 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['8','7','5','6'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 46,
            question: 'What is 4 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['9','8','6','7'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 47,
            question: 'What is 4 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['10','8','9','7'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 48,
            question: 'What is 4 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['10','9','8','11'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 49,
            question: 'What is 4 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['11','9','10','12'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 50,
            question: 'What is 4 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['11','12','13','10'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 51,
            question: 'What is 5 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['5','4','3','2'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 52,
            question: 'What is 5 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['6','4','5','3'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 53,
            question: 'What is 5 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['7','6','4','5'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 54,
            question: 'What is 5 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['5','8','6','7'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 55,
            question: 'What is 5 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['9','7','8','6'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 56,
            question: 'What is 5 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['10','9','8','7'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 57,
            question: 'What is 5 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['8','10','9','11'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 58,
            question: 'What is 5 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['9','10','12','11'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 59,
            question: 'What is 5 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['10','12','13','11'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 60,
            question: 'What is 5 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['13','11','14','12'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 61,
            question: 'What is 6 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['4','5','3','6'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 62,
            question: 'What is 6 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['5','6','7','4'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 63,
            question: 'What is 6 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['8','6','7','5'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 64,
            question: 'What is 6 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['9','6','8','7'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 65,
            question: 'What is 6 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['7','8','9','10'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 66,
            question: 'What is 6 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['9','10','8','11'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 67,
            question: 'What is 6 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['9','11','10','12'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 68,
            question: 'What is 6 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['13','12','11','10'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 69,
            question: 'What is 6 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['11','12','14','13'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 70,
            question: 'What is 6 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['14','12','15','13'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 71,
            question: 'What is 7 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['5','6','4','7'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 72,
            question: 'What is 7 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['5','8','6','7'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 73,
            question: 'What is 7 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['6','9','7','8'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 74,
            question: 'What is 7 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['8','10','7','9'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 75,
            question: 'What is 7 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['9','8','11','10'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 76,
            question: 'What is 7 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['10','11','9','12'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 77,
            question: 'What is 7 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['13','11','12','10'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 78,
            question: 'What is 7 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['12','14','13','11'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 79,
            question: 'What is 7 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['12','15','13','14'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 80,
            question: 'What is 7 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['15','14','13','16'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 81,
            question: 'What is 8 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['8','5','7','6'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 82,
            question: 'What is 8 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['8','7','9','6'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 83,
            question: 'What is 8 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['8','9','10','7'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 84,
            question: 'What is 8 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['11','10','8','9'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 85,
            question: 'What is 8 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['12','9','11','10'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 86,
            question: 'What is 8 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['13','12','10','11'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 87,
            question: 'What is 8 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['11','12','14','13'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 88,
            question: 'What is 8 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['14','13','15','12'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 89,
            question: 'What is 8 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['13','14','16','15'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 90,
            question: 'What is 8 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['17','15','14','16'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 91,
            question: 'What is 9 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['6','9','7','8'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 92,
            question: 'What is 9 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['9','8','10','7'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 93,
            question: 'What is 9 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['9','11','8','10'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 94,
            question: 'What is 9 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['9','11','12','10'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 95,
            question: 'What is 9 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['11','13','12','10'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 96,
            question: 'What is 9 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['13','12','14','11'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 97,
            question: 'What is 9 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['15','13','14','12'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 98,
            question: 'What is 9 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['15','14','13','16'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 99,
            question: 'What is 9 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['17','15','14','16'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 100,
            question: 'What is 9 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['17','16','18','15'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
]
